ticketnews.com 2011-11-28

# TicketNews - Privacy Policy | TicketNews

## Privacy Policy

_Last Updated - May 2011_

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices of [TicketNews.com](http://www.ticketnews.com/) regarding its treatment of personally identifiable information or other information that may be collected through common use of the site and its products and services.

**This Privacy Policy will address:**  

> • Sites Covered by This Policy  
>  • User Information: Collection and Use  
>  • Security  
>  • User Accounts  
>  • Subscription E-mail Services  
>  • TicketNewsfeed Widget  
>  • Opting-Out and User Access to and Control Over Information  
>  • Amendments

* * *

**SITES COVERED BY THIS POLICY**

This Privacy Policy applies to [TicketNews.com](http://www.ticketnews.com/) and all internal pages open to public navigation and intended for public use.

TicketNews.com provides links to external and third-party Web sites for the information and convenience of its users. We are not responsible for, nor does this Privacy Policy apply to, the practices or content of those companies or individuals, or the third-party advertisers on TicketNews.com. We encourage our users to read the Privacy Policies of sites linked through TicketNews.com before providing any personal information.

**USER INFORMATION: COLLECTION AND USE**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. TicketNews.com gathers 1.) personally identifiable information (e.g. names, e-mail addresses), and 2.) non-personally identifiable information (e.g. IP addresses, pages viewed).

TicketNews.com only has access to personally identifiable information provided by and with the full consent and intent of the user via on-site submission forms or any user-initiated contact. This information is used only as it relates to the user's intended actions (e.g. registering for a user account, or subscribing to a mailing list). We do not sell or rent this information to anyone.

TicketNews.com also collects non-personally identifiable information regarding user interaction with and navigation of the site. Our third-party Web analytic services are provided via Google Analytics. (Refer to the official [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/analytics/) for information on their methods of data collection.) This information is used only by TicketNews.com for the purpose of site administration and bettering the services provided to our users. We do not sell or rent this information to anyone.

TicketNews.com will respond to verified law enforcement, or other governmental department requests or subpoenas relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, TicketNews.com will disclose information relevant to the investigation. TicketNews.com reserves the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that it believes, in good faith, to be unlawful. 

**SECURITY**

TicketNews.com aims to serve and protect its users against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information. Our servers and information stores are protected by reasonable security measures. Any sensitive information requested on behalf of TicketNews.com for the completion of a merchandise order is handled through a secure processing page operated by PayPal. (Refer to the official [PayPal Privacy Policy](https://cms.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/?&cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US) for details regarding their operation and policies.) Completion of any PayPal-based transaction indicates user acceptance of PayPal's policies.

**USER ACCOUNTS**

Access to all public content and basic levels of functionality is free and available to all site users. User accounts are also available and allow the creation of an identifying username, but are not mandatory for regular site use. Personal information used in the creation of the user account (e.g. name, e-mail address) remains private and is not visible to other site users. 

Upon creating a user account, an account activation e-mail will be sent by TicketNews.com to the address provided by the user. This e-mail includes a one-time password, which the user is asked to change when first logging into the new account. Users retain sole responsibility for creating and maintaining a secure password for their account; a new password may be created under the "Edit" tab of "My Account" when logged in. In the event of a forgotten password, the user may request a new password, which is delivered via automated e-mail and not recorded or filed by TicketNews.com.

Users are free to delete their accounts at any time; the option is available under the "Edit" tab of "My Account." For assistance in deleting an account, contact [editorial@ticketnews.com](mailto:editorial@ticketnews.com). Please provide the username to be deleted; the e-mail request must originate from the address used to create the account. Accounts deemed to be suspicious, spam, or otherwise harmful to the user in question or the TicketNews.com community as a whole may be deleted at the sole discretion of TicketNews.com and without prior notice.

**SUBSCRIPTION E-MAIL SERVICES**

TicketNews.com may send daily and weekly newsletters, breaking reports, special promotions and other forms of subscription e-mail to its users. These services are provided free of charge to users who have consented to and provided contact information explicitly for the receipt of e-mail communications from TicketNews.com.

**TICKETNEWSFEED WIDGET**

TicketNews.com offers, as a convenience, the option to install the TicketNewsfeed Widget on the user's personal Web site, blog, social networking profile or other Internet-based platform. The Widget is hosted by TicketNews.com and presented as-is; its code may not be "hacked" or modified by the user other than via basic color customization options offered on TicketNews.com.

Operation or use of the Widget does not require any input or storage of the user's personal information. The feed employs a non-personal tracking code for general analytic purposes related to overall click-through rates from the Widget's in-bound links to TicketNews.com and its content. 

**OPTING-OUT AND USER ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION ******

Any user can do the following, at any time, by contacting us via [editorial@ticketnews.com](mailto:editorial@ticketnews.com):  

> • Opt out of any future contact from us;  
>  • See what data we have about that user, if any;  
>  • Change or correct any data we have about that user;  
>  • Have us delete any data we have about that user; and  
>  • Express any concern the user has about our handling of that user's data. 

To unsubscribe from any mass e-mail communication sent by TicketNews.com, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each e-mail. Users experiencing difficulty with the unsubscribe process or continuing to receive unsolicited communications should contact [editorial@ticketnews.com](mailto:editorial@ticketnews.com). Unsubscribe requests must include the name of the newsletter from which the user wishes to be unsubscribed.

Users may discontinue use of the TicketNewsfeed Widget at any time by simply removing the Widget's code from any platform on which it was installed by the user. Any similar RSS feed installed by the user to read or view content from TicketNews.com may be removed or discontinued by the user at any time, following uninstall/delete protocol set forth by the user's chosen RSS platform. 

If a user feels that we are not abiding by this Privacy Policy, the user should contact us immediately by e-mail at [editorial@ticketnews.com](mailto:editorial@ticketnews.com).

**AMENDMENTS**

TicketNews reserves the right to amend this policy at any time. Policy changes and updates will be posted on this page. Continued use of the site after policy changes have been posted indicates user acceptance of the updated policy.
